wholemom.com 2016-12-26

# Privacy Policy - Whole Mom

[This statement discloses the privacy practices for the WholeMom.com website. By visiting WholeMom.com, you are accepting the practices described herein. Because Whole Mom wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and notify you of the following:](http://www.wholemom.com/sweepstakes/top-5-cash-sweepstakes/)

[The information we collect helps us ensure that our services are best designed to meet your needs. We receive and store any information that you enter on any registration page. Typically these will be registration forms for sweepstakes, surveys or other promotions. If you are giving us information in order to participate in a survey, sweepstakes or other promotion, your participation is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. If some information is required and some is optional, we will identify the required information. We collect both contact and other information.](http://www.wholemom.com/sweepstakes/top-5-cash-sweepstakes/)

[Contact information consists of the information that we can use to contact you if, for example, you win one of the contests or promotions sponsored by Whole Mom and/or its affiliates and partners. This consists of your name, your e-mail address, IP address and possibly your mailing address, telephone and facsimile number. Visitors who supply Whole Mom with their postal address may receive periodic postal mailings from us with information on new products and services or upcoming events. They may also receive mailings from other reputable companies.](http://www.wholemom.com/sweepstakes/top-5-cash-sweepstakes/)

[Profile data also is collected at our site. Depending on the specific Whole Mom products for which a user (“User”) registers, various information will be requested. We use this data to tailor the visitor’s experience through our interest-focused e-mails. By obtaining this information, we can provide our Users with specific content that we think they might be interested in, according to their preferences and interests. The User may include only the information he or she feels comfortable including. However, the omission of certain information may limit the value of the experience for the User. As a result, the more information we have about a User, the more valuable the WholeMom.com experience will be for that User. In addition, Whole Mom provides services for direct marketing applications including lookup and reference, data enhancement, suppression and validation.](http://www.wholemom.com/sweepstakes/top-5-cash-sweepstakes/)

[Whole Mom does not send unsolicited or “spam” e-mail. We use User information in a number of ways, including:](http://www.wholemom.com/sweepstakes/top-5-cash-sweepstakes/)

  1. [to send personalized, targeted information to the User in the form of e-mail messages and/or direct mail;](http://www.wholemom.com/sweepstakes/top-5-cash-sweepstakes/)
  2. [to send targeted advertising that allows us to provide our service at no or little cost to the Users;](http://www.wholemom.com/sweepstakes/top-5-cash-sweepstakes/)
  3. [to send promotions and coupons based on their interests;](http://www.wholemom.com/sweepstakes/top-5-cash-sweepstakes/)
  4. [to contact Users for feedback and surveys;](http://www.wholemom.com/sweepstakes/top-5-cash-sweepstakes/)
  5. [to monitor and improve its internal operations, as well as to ensure that it properly performs the services requested and bills properly where appropriate; and](http://www.wholemom.com/sweepstakes/top-5-cash-sweepstakes/)
  6. [to send Users other information about Whole Mom and/or its products.](http://www.wholemom.com/sweepstakes/top-5-cash-sweepstakes/)

[Note: You will always be given the opportunity to immediately and permanently unsubscribe from these mailings.](http://www.wholemom.com/sweepstakes/top-5-cash-sweepstakes/)

[When you register with WholeMom.com, you may receive offers from us or our marketing partners. Our marketing partners may use this information to make offers to you in your areas of interest or other offers. Our marketing partners wishing to contact you either give their e-mail message to us and we deliver it to you, or we provide your contact information to them so they can deliver messages directly to you. It is solely at your discretion if you choose to provide additional personally identifiable information to a marketer by making a purchase, requesting additional information, or communicating directly with the company or organization after using its website. We may also use outside companies to execute the marketing campaigns on our behalf or on behalf of some of our marketing partners. We will share your e-mail, name & other information that you give us that is necessary for these third parties to provide these services. These third parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purposes of providing these services.](http://www.wholemom.com/sweepstakes/top-5-cash-sweepstakes/)

[Certain information or services offered or provided on or through the Site from time to time may be provided on or through other sites operated by or in conjunction with third party providers (“Partners”). These sites may have the same “look and feel” of the Site, and are often cobranded, such that a Partner’s logo or name may appear on the site, or the Partner’s name may appear in the URL. Aggregate or personally identifiable information collected about you on these sites may be shared by Whole Mom with that Partner. A Partner will not rent, sell, or disclose any of your personally identifiable information to third parties unless you consent to its doing so, for example, by opting-in while on a particular site to receive information or offers from a Partner’s affiliates, partners, or other third parties.](http://www.wholemom.com/sweepstakes/top-5-cash-sweepstakes/)

[You acknowledge that we do not monitor, control or endorse the information collection or privacy practices of any third parties, any co-branded or other affiliated sites which may or may not be owned or operated by or in conjunction with Whole Mom, or any credit card order processors, product shippers or other third parties who provide services throughout the Site. Accordingly, Whole Mom assumes no liability or responsibility for the information collection and privacy practices of any third party. In addition, Whole Mom is not responsible for the content of any third party websites, including a third party’s use of any cookies or any other information (such as IP address, browser type or operating system) collected when you “click-through” links to their sites or view advertisements served by them. Even though certain information collected by such third parties might not identify you personally, we strongly encourage you to become familiar with their privacy practices, and to contact such third parties if you have any questions about their respective privacy policies. In addition, the Site may provide links to other Internet websites or resources (“Linked Sites”). Whole Mom neither controls nor endorses such Linked Sites nor have we reviewed or approved any content that appears on such Linked Sites. You acknowledge and agree that Whole Mom is not responsible for the legality, accuracy or inappropriate nature of any content, advertising, products or other materials on or available from such Linked Sites. You further acknowledge and agree that Whole Mom shall not be responsible or liable, directly or indirectly, for any damage or loss caused or alleged to be caused by or in connection with use of or reliance on any such content, goods, and services available on or through any such Linked Site.](http://www.wholemom.com/sweepstakes/top-5-cash-sweepstakes/)

[We may set and access WholeMom.com cookies on your computer. These are used to automatically differentiate you from other users of our website. We sometimes let other companies that show advertisements on some of our pages set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies’ use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not our privacy policy. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to our cookies.](http://www.wholemom.com/sweepstakes/top-5-cash-sweepstakes/)

[We will not release any information about you, including your email address, to any third party other than the exceptions noted above. We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect personal information about you.](http://www.wholemom.com/sweepstakes/top-5-cash-sweepstakes/)

[We comply with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.](http://www.wholemom.com/sweepstakes/top-5-cash-sweepstakes/)

[To remove your User information from our mailing list(s) so as not to receive future communications from us or to no longer receive our service, please email privacy@wholecustomer.com and specify your request. If you have submitted personal information under more than one e-mail account, you must make this request from each account that you have used. WholeMom.com will use commercially reasonable efforts to delete records from our mailing list when we receive requests to do so. Please allow up to 48 hours to be completely removed from our database. This Privacy Policy is subject to change from time to time, so please check back periodically. Use of the services offered at this site constitutes acceptance of the terms of this Policy.](http://www.wholemom.com/sweepstakes/top-5-cash-sweepstakes/)

[Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to comply with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your prior consent.](http://www.wholemom.com/sweepstakes/top-5-cash-sweepstakes/)

[If you have any questions regarding this privacy policy please contact us at: privacy@wholecustomer.com. Whole Mom may transfer, sell or assign information concerning your use of this Site, including without limitation, personally identifiable information that you provide and other information concerning your use of the Site, to third parties, as a result of a sale, merger, consolidation, changing control, transfer of substantial assets, reorganization or liquidation of WholeMom.com.](http://www.wholemom.com/sweepstakes/top-5-cash-sweepstakes/)

[Whole Mom or its successors and assigns may amend the terms and conditions of the Privacy Policy at any time, or substitute a different Agreement by posting a revised version, on the Whole Mom Sites. Please refer to our site periodically for updates. Amendments shall become effective upon posting. As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy certain assets. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets. If WholeMom.com or its assets are acquired, customer information will of course be one of the transferred assets.](http://www.wholemom.com/sweepstakes/top-5-cash-sweepstakes/)

[We may sell, brand or share your personal information that you supply to us with other 3rd party businesses so they can bring selected retail opportunities via direct mail, e-mail or telemarketing for the privacy policy.](http://www.wholemom.com/sweepstakes/top-5-cash-sweepstakes/)

[If you are not in agreement with the terms of this Policy, please unsubscribe from the WholeMom.com email list, by visiting (unsubscribe link) or write to us at:](http://www.wholemom.com/sweepstakes/top-5-cash-sweepstakes/)

[Whole Mom  
193 Branthaven St.  
Ottawa, Ontario K4A 0H7 Canada](http://www.wholemom.com/sweepstakes/top-5-cash-sweepstakes/)

[and request to be removed. If you feel that Whole Mom is not abiding by its posted privacy policy, please contact us by email here: privacy@wholecustomer.com or write us at the above address.](http://www.wholemom.com/sweepstakes/top-5-cash-sweepstakes/)
